<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_4_2_0">
		<text>안녕, 문지기 </text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_4_2_1">
		<text>반갑네. 리만스크로 가는 건가? 레시가 아니었다면... 어쨌든, 어서 오서와. 돈을 내야 할거야... 그리고 우리 순찰대에 발각되지 않도록 조심해 - 그들은 협상의 일부가 아니거든.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_4_1_0">
		<text>여기 돈.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_4_1_1">
		<text>좋아. 내가 다리에 있는 경비병에게 신호를 줄 거야. 일단 도착하면, 대화 상대는 "문지기"다. 침착하게 행동하고, 스카의 실종을 밝혀줄 수 있는 무언가를 찾아.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_0">
		<text>레시, 맞지?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_1">
		<text>그래, 가이드가 필요한가, 아니면 다른 걸 원하나?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_2">
		<text>네 과거에 대해 알고 있어. 난 네 도움이 필요해, 용병</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_3">
		<text>어... 어떤 도움이 필요하지?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_4">
		<text>붉은 숲에 있는 다리를 지키고 있는 용병들에게 얘기 좀 해주겠어? 난 리만스크로 가야 해. 불편할 수도 있다는 건 알지만, 용병 스카가 남긴 흔적을 찾아 보겠다고 약속할 수 있어.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_3_2_5">
		<text>흐음, 내가 오랫동안 조직에 몸담지 않았다는 걸 알아야해. 누가 다리에서 조직을 운영하는지조차 확실하지 않아. 몇 군데 연줄이 있긴 하지만 시간이 좀 필요할 것 같군 그리고 약간의 돈도. 15만 루블, 그 이하는 안돼.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_0">
		<text>당신 조직의 역사에 대해 들은 게 있어. 조사하고 싶다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_1">
		<text>You looking for something, or what? Hah, listen. You have virtually no chance of surviving in those areas - but even if you do, finding information about our stay there ain't exactly gonna be a walk in the park.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_2">
		<text>Aren't you interested? Or is there something you want in return?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_3">
		<text>Hmm... You can help us take out a pack of bloodsuckers in the swamp, and maybe then I'll share what I've got with you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_4">
		<text>Fine, give me the coordinates.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_1_5">
		<text>There you go - have fun.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_2_0">
		<text>It's done. What info do you have?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_2_1">
		<text>So I've heard - well done. You're a good fighter and I trust you, so I'll give you what you need. The boys have probably told you about the assault at that damned bridge in Limansk. In case you don't know... Back then, in the city - as well as the surrounding area in the Red Forest - mercenaries were in charge of everything. Of course, they aren't going to just lower the bridge for you, but there is a live participant in those events - they call him Forester. It was him, along with Scar, who somehow agreed that a group of "standards" would lower the bridge while our fighters protected them from the other shore. Here, I'll give you info on a route between the Army Warehouses and the Red Forest - use it to find Forester and talk to him. And here's a reward for the bloodsucker cleanup.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="look_for_cs_history_part_1_2_2">
		<text>Thank you.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="mlr_inventory_box_unuse">
		<text>Locked stash</text>
	</string>

	<string id="totaliz_helper_mlr_text">
		<text>For a different perspective on the area, press the tilde key or \ to open the console, and enter: demo_record 1. The camera is controlled using the W, A, S and D keys along with CTRL. To exit, press the ESC key.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_pda_mlr_descr">
		<text>A PDA containing possible information on routes between different areas. Its message history is inaccessible due to the presence of a password lock.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_new_path_mlr">
		<text>A route between two areas has become accessible.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="killer_bridge_trader_mlr_task_1_name">
		<text>Find %s</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_bridge_trader_mlr_task_1_text">
		<text>The mercenaries have asked me to get hold of %s.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_bridge_trader_mlr_task_1_about">
		<text>Our soldiers need some equipment, can you get it for us?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_bridge_trader_mlr_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>Our soldiers need %s, will you retrieve it for us?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_bridge_trader_mlr_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Thank you, here's your reward.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="killer_bridge_trader_mlr_task_2_name">
		<text>Find a %s artefact</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_bridge_trader_mlr_task_2_text">
		<text>A mercenary needs a %s.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_bridge_trader_mlr_task_2_about">
		<text>Our soldiers could use a few artefacts, it'll be tough getting through Limansk without them. Could you help us find one?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_bridge_trader_mlr_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>Our soldiers could use a few artefacts, it'll be tough getting through Limansk without them. Could you help us find a %s?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="killer_bridge_trader_mlr_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Many thanks. Here, have this.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_1_1">
		<text>Find and kill the bloodsuckers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_1_2">
		<text>Return to Cold</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_1_3">
		<text>So, he's afraid to send me "this way", but it's okay if I'm going to fight against swamp bloodsuckers? Cheap salesmen even in Clear Sky, I see..</text>
	</string>

	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_2_1">
		<text>Following the tracks of Clear Sky: talk with Forester</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_descr_2_1">
		<text>Cold told me that the immediate participant of those events is Forester and gave me his coordinates. I have to talk to him and get to Limansk.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_3_1">
		<text>Following the tracks of Clear Sky: find Leshiy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_3_2">
		<text>Following the tracks of Clear Sky: talk to Leshiy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_descr_3_1">
		<text>Well, back to the military. It turns out that the key figure of that battle for the bridge was under my nose all this time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_descr_3_2">
		<text>I only have to reach an agreement with Leshiy himself, I hope this will end my quest.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_4_1">
		<text>Following the tracks of Clear Sky: collect 150000 RU and bring it to Leshiy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_4_3">
		<text>Following the tracks of Clear Sky: go to a meeting with Gatekeeper</text>
	</string>
	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_4_4">
		<text>Following the tracks of Clear Sky: speak with Gatekeeper</text>
	</string>

	<string id="task_look_for_cs_history_part_descr_4_1">
		<text>Finally, soon I'll be on the other side of the bridge and those running errands will end.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bridge_is_open_message">
		<text>Gatekeeper:\nI see someone. Hey, stalker! Come over here, got a few words for you.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
