<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Upgrading Parts
-->

<string_table>

<!-- Outfits -->
	<string id="st_upgr_o_health">
		<text>생명 보조 시스템 프로토타입</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_health_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 착용자의 건강 상태를 관찰하고 비타민, 아드레날린이나 기타 신진대사 물질들을 필요한 만큼 공급해주는 통합 시스템이 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_bleed">
		<text>상처 치료 시스템 프로토타입</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_bleed_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 야전에서 약품 사용을 지속적으로 관리하기 위한 의료용 기구가 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_armor">
		<text>강화된 방탄용 안감</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_armor_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 다양한 종류의 케블라, 티타늄, 베릴, 알루미늄 그리고 카본 섬유 판 및 그물망들을 포함하고 있습니다. 높은 점착력과 훌륭한 총탄 저지력을 가지고 있습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_damage">
		<text>보조 장갑판</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_damage_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 특수하게 제작된 다양한 소재의 장갑판이 포함되어 있어, 방탄력을 약간 높여줍니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_durability">
		<text>견고한 장갑판과 옷감</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_durability_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 중장비에 사용되는 티타늄과 알루미늄 합금으로 된 튼튼한 장갑판과, 가벼운 장비에 사용되는 폴리머 안감이 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_power">
		<text>플라스틱 및 합성 부품</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_power_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 다양한 장갑복에서 사용되었던 합성 섬유와 플라스틱 부품들이 포함되어 있으며, 방어구의 무게를 줄여 기동성과 내구성을 향상시키기 위해 고안되었습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_chem">
		<text>화학적 방화 소재와 안감</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_chem_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 화학적인 영향으로부터 방어구의 보호 성능을 향상시킬 수 있는 유해한 직물 및 재료 세트가 들어 있습니다. 이러한 소재들은 연소 시 가스 생성 과정에서의 화학 반응에 간섭할 수 있는 한편, 몇몇 소재에서는 보호막 내부에서 부풀어오르는 화학 물질들을 포함하고 있어, 더욱 강한 단열 효과를 제공합니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_burn">
		<text>방화 옷감 및 안감</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_burn_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 불이 번지는 것을 늦추거나 막아주고, 불의 세기를 약화시키는 독특한 기능을 가진 보호용 옷감과 소재들이 포함되어 있습니다. 이러한 소재들 중 일부는 다양한 길이, 너비, 두께와 형태를 가진 마그네슘 성분이 포함된 내화성 물질입니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_shock">
		<text>절연용 직물 및 안감</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_shock_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 보호용 콘스탄탄, 마그네슘 그리고 실리콘 안감 세트가 포함되어 있으며, 방어구에 가해지는 전기 충격을 줄여주도록 고안되었습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_psi">
		<text>보호 코팅된 피복</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_psi_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 머리 보호구나 장갑복에 사용되는 코팅용 안감과 알루미늄 처리된 내피 세트와 함께, 정신파의 효과를 약간 감소시켜 주는 전파 방해용 고무 소재가 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_rad">
		<text>활성 필터와 방사능 방호 소재</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_rad_desc">
		<text>보호용 필터 한 세트로, 호흡기를 통해 신체로 다양한 독성 물질이나 화학 물질들이 침투하는 것을 막아줍니다. 알파 및 감마선 입자의 강도를 저감시키기 위한 고밀도 소재들 또한 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_carry">
		<text>무게 분산용 고정 시스템</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_carry_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 무게 분산을 위한 다양한 고정끈 세트가 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_arty">
		<text>부착물 고정용 물품</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_arty_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 동시에 사용할 수 있는 모듈이나 아티팩트 컨테이너의 숫자를 늘려주는 의복 벨트 부착물이 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_run">
		<text>유압식 서보 드라이브 증폭 시스템</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_run_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 1세대 및 2세대 외골격에 사용되는 강화 프로토타입 서보 드라이브가 포함되어 있어, 사용자가 외골격을 입고 달릴 수 있도록 합니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_weight">
		<text>경량화 소재</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_weight_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 다양한 길이, 너비, 두께 및 모양은 물론 다양한 기능을 가진 경량 폴리머 소재 세트가 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>

<!-- Weapons -->
	<string id="st_upgr_w_weight">
		<text>이동형 역가중 부품</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_weight_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of lightweight polymer components for various types of weapons. The fashion for polymer components has not only paid off, but it has also become quite a popular upgrade.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_muffle">
		<text>총열 외부 나사깎기용 부품</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_muffle_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of external threading components for various types of weapons. External threading allows a silencer to be installed.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_grenade_mount">
		<text>총열 하단 유탄발사기 거치대</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_grenade_mount_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of external underbarrel grenade launcher mounts for various types of weapons.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_reliability">
		<text>자동 가스 조절기</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_reliability_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of special regulator mechanism for various types of weapons. It protects the weapon from dirt.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_speed">
		<text>총열 추가 나사모양 홈</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_speed_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of additional threaded canals for various types of weapons. Installation of a barrel with additional threaded canals improves bullet speed and weapon accuracy at the cost of a considerable increase in recoil.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_recoil">
		<text>추가 가스 피스톤</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_recoil_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of additional gas pistons for various types of weapons. A second piston moves the counter-weight, compensating for the bolt mechanism movement impulse.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_magazine">
		<text>대용량 탄창 세트</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_magazine_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of magazines for various types of weapons with higher capacity for calibres.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_scope">
		<text>광학식 조준기 거치대 세트</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_scope_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of optical scopes for various types of weapons. Mounting includes scopes for close, medium and long range combat.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_dispersion">
		<text>균형유지 부품</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_dispersion_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of balancing elements for various types of weapons. Synthetic elements installed onto rods ensures that they move strictly as intended, increasing accuracy.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_calibre">
		<text>구경 전환 부품 세트</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_calibre_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of calibre components for various types of weapons. A complex, integrated alteration of the weapon's mechanical and automated parts, which allows its calibre to be changed at the cost of reliability.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_inertion">
		<text>다양한 모양의 인체공학적 총몸</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_inertion_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of ergonomic receiver for various types of weapons. A modification used exclusively for barrels with solid bullpup receivers, which simplifies maintenance of the weapon.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_rpm">
		<text>티타늄 복귀 장치 지지대</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_rpm_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of titanium rods for various types of weapons. Titanium rods can endure a much higher rate of fire than regular rods.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_scope_mount">
		<text>광학식 조준경 거치대 세트</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_scope_mount_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of optical mounts for various types of weapons. Allowing installation of a mount for attachment of an optical scope.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_firemode">
		<text>방아쇠 기계장치 세트</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_firemode_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of trigger mechanism for various types of weapons. Improvement of the weapon's automatic parts suitable for different burst and automated fire modes.\n \n</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
