<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Upgrading Parts
-->

<string_table>

<!-- Outfits -->
	<string id="st_upgr_o_health">
		<text>생명 보조 시스템 프로토타입</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_health_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 착용자의 건강 상태를 관찰하고 비타민, 아드레날린이나 기타 신진대사 물질들을 필요한 만큼 공급해주는 통합 시스템이 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_bleed">
		<text>상처 치료 시스템 프로토타입</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_bleed_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 야전에서 약품 사용을 지속적으로 관리하기 위한 의료용 기구가 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_armor">
		<text>강화된 방탄용 안감</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_armor_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 다양한 종류의 케블라, 티타늄, 베릴, 알루미늄 그리고 카본 섬유 판 및 그물망들을 포함하고 있습니다. 높은 점착력과 훌륭한 총탄 저지력을 가지고 있습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_damage">
		<text>보조 장갑판</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_damage_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 특수하게 제작된 다양한 소재의 장갑판이 포함되어 있어, 방탄력을 약간 높여줍니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_durability">
		<text>견고한 장갑판과 옷감</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_durability_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 중장비에 사용되는 티타늄과 알루미늄 합금으로 된 튼튼한 장갑판과, 가벼운 장비에 사용되는 폴리머 안감이 포함되어 있습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_power">
		<text>플라스틱 및 합성 부품</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_power_desc">
		<text>이 패키지에는 다양한 장갑복에서 사용되었던 합성 섬유와 플라스틱 부품들이 포함되어 있으며, 방어구의 무게를 줄여 기동성과 내구성을 향상시키기 위해 고안되었습니다.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_chem">
		<text>화학적 방화 소재와 안감</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_chem_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of hazardous fabrics and materials which can improve the protective performance of suits of armour against chemical effects. They can interrupt the chemical reaction in the gas phase of combustion, while some contain chemicals that cause swelling up behind the protective layer, providing even more insulation.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_burn">
		<text>방화 옷감 및 안감</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_burn_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of protective fabrics and materials with unqiue properties to slow or stop the spread of fire or reduce its intensity. Some are fireproof materials containing magnesium elements of varying length, width, thickness and shape.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_shock">
		<text>절연용 직물 및 안감</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_shock_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of protective constantan, magnesium and silicone inserts, designed to reduce the impact of electrical charges on armour.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_psi">
		<text>보호 코팅된 피복</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_psi_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of screening inserts and aluminized layers for helmets and armoured suits, with radio-repellent rubber to slightly reducing the effects of psy-influences.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_rad">
		<text>활성 필터와 방사능 방호 소재</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_rad_desc">
		<text>A set of protective filters, preventing the entry of various poisons and chemicals into the body through respiratory systems. In addition of high-density materials to reduce the intensity of alpha and gamma particles.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_carry">
		<text>무게 분산용 고정 시스템</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_carry_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of various fasteners for load distribution.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_arty">
		<text>부착물 고정용 물품</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_arty_desc">
		<text>This package contains a suit belt attachment to increase the number of simultaneously usable modules and artefact containers.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_run">
		<text>유압식 서보 드라이브 증폭 시스템</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_run_desc">
		<text>This package contains enhanced prototypical servo drives for first and second generation exoskeletons, allowing the user to sprint.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_o_weight">
		<text>경량화 소재</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_o_weight_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of lightweight polymeric materials of varying length, width, thickness and shape, as well as various properties.\n \n</text>
	</string>

<!-- Weapons -->
	<string id="st_upgr_w_weight">
		<text>이동형 역가중 부품</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_weight_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of lightweight polymer components for various types of weapons. The fashion for polymer components has not only paid off, but it has also become quite a popular upgrade.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_muffle">
		<text>총열 외부 나사깎기용 부품</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_muffle_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of external threading components for various types of weapons. External threading allows a silencer to be installed.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_grenade_mount">
		<text>총열 하단 유탄발사기 거치대</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_grenade_mount_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of external underbarrel grenade launcher mounts for various types of weapons.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_reliability">
		<text>자동 가스 조절기</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_reliability_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of special regulator mechanism for various types of weapons. It protects the weapon from dirt.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_speed">
		<text>총열 추가 나사모양 홈</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_speed_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of additional threaded canals for various types of weapons. Installation of a barrel with additional threaded canals improves bullet speed and weapon accuracy at the cost of a considerable increase in recoil.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_recoil">
		<text>추가 가스 피스톤</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_recoil_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of additional gas pistons for various types of weapons. A second piston moves the counter-weight, compensating for the bolt mechanism movement impulse.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_magazine">
		<text>대용량 탄창 세트</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_magazine_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of magazines for various types of weapons with higher capacity for calibres.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_scope">
		<text>광학식 조준기 거치대 세트</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_scope_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of optical scopes for various types of weapons. Mounting includes scopes for close, medium and long range combat.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_dispersion">
		<text>균형유지 부품</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_dispersion_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of balancing elements for various types of weapons. Synthetic elements installed onto rods ensures that they move strictly as intended, increasing accuracy.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_calibre">
		<text>구경 전환 부품 세트</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_calibre_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of calibre components for various types of weapons. A complex, integrated alteration of the weapon's mechanical and automated parts, which allows its calibre to be changed at the cost of reliability.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_inertion">
		<text>다양한 모양의 인체공학적 총몸</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_inertion_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of ergonomic receiver for various types of weapons. A modification used exclusively for barrels with solid bullpup receivers, which simplifies maintenance of the weapon.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_rpm">
		<text>티타늄 복귀 장치 지지대</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_rpm_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of titanium rods for various types of weapons. Titanium rods can endure a much higher rate of fire than regular rods.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_scope_mount">
		<text>광학식 조준경 거치대 세트</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_scope_mount_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of optical mounts for various types of weapons. Allowing installation of a mount for attachment of an optical scope.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_upgr_w_firemode">
		<text>방아쇠 기계장치 세트</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_upgr_w_firemode_desc">
		<text>This package contains a set of trigger mechanism for various types of weapons. Improvement of the weapon's automatic parts suitable for different burst and automated fire modes.\n \n</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
