<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<!--===========================================================
<
< QUEST ITEMS TEXT  STRINGS
<	CoC 1.4.07 - DoctorX Questlines 1.6
<
<	Modified by: DoctorX
<	Last revised: October 06, 2016
<
<===========================================================-->


<string_table>

	<!-- DRX Storyline Documents Quest Item -->
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_1_name">
		<text>서류</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_1_desc">
		<text>강력하게 암호화된 서류들입니다. 많은 부분은 일반적인 능력으로는 해석할 수 없는 수준으로 되어 있지만, 서론 부분 정도는 가능할 것처럼 보입니다. 물론 당연하겠지만, 그런 일까지 하는 건 인건비를 넘어선 일이 될 것입니다... 임무를 완수하려면 그저 이런 서류들을 가져다주면 될 뿐이고, 굳이 이런 걸 해석할 수고는 들이지 않아야 할 것입니다.\n \n"Jxu Pedu ev Qbyudqjyed - Jxu Hebu ev Ucyiiyedi yd Ckjqdj Hufhetksjyed\nro Fhevuiieh Q.R. Ijhkwqjiao\n \nQrijhqsj\nQi tucedijhqjut ro Fhevuiieh Xuhcqdd, yj yi ademd jxqj ucyiiyedi sqd fhetksu qhjuvqsji qdt qdecqbyui, mxybu Fhevuiieh Iqaxqhel xqi tucedijhqjut jxqj ucyiiyedi sqd pecryvo bylydw ruydwi. Rkj mxqj qhu jxu uvvusji ev ucyiiyedi ed xkcqd hucqydi?\n \nHuikbji muhu erjqydut ro buqlydw jxu sehfiui ev ijqbauhi sqwut yd efud qyh tkhydw ucyiiyedi. Qvjuh ckbjyfbu juiji, jxu unfuhycudji muhu hufuqjut myjx jxu retyui ev xkcqdeyt ckjqdji iksx qi jxu vqrbut idehai qdt rbeetiksauhi.\n \nMxqj mu vekdt mqi jxqj qd ucyiiyed, mxud secydw ydje sedjqsj myjx q iaubujqb sehfiu, xqi q sxqdsu je shuqju q "cekbqwu" - q bylydw sqij ev vbuix cqtu vhec qdecqbeki fxudecudq, mxysx jxud huqdycqjui jxu reto. Cekbqwui sqd jqau jxu vehc ev idehai, rbeetiksauhi, pecryvyut xkcqdi qi mubb qi iuucydwbo dehcqb xkcqdi, qdt yd qbb sqiui sqd ru tyijydwkyixut vhec jxuyh jhkbo bylydw sekdjuhfqhji ro jxuyh tuqjxbo whuo fqbbeh. Cekbqwui mxe ceij huiucrbut dehcqb xkcqdi unxyryjut jxu qrybyjo je secckdysqju rkj hugkyhut iutqjyed qi jxuo ydlqhyqrbo tyifbqout unjhucu fqhqdeyq, tubkiyedi, eh q tuiyhu je uisqfu ydje jxu kdademd.\n \nSedsbkiyed: q fejudjyqb unfbqdqjyed veh hufhetksjyed qcedw jxu kdyiun ideha secckdyjyui xqi ruud erjqydut. Vkhjxuhcehu, jxuhu yi dem q isyudjyvys hqjyedqbu veh eriuhlydw fhefuh rkhyqb skijeci yd jxu Pedu, buij mu sxeeiu je vuut yji tqdwuhi ydijuqt.\ncc -2018"
 </text>
	</string>

	<!-- DRX Storyline Locked Case Quest Item -->
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_2_name">
		<text>잠겨진 상자</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_2_desc">
		<text>잠겨진 상자입니다. 안에 무엇이 들어있는지는 모르지만 꽤 무겁습니다. 들고 갈 만한 가치가 있기를 바랄 뿐입니다.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- DRX Storyline PDA Quest Item -->
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_3_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_3_desc">
		<text>암호화된 PDA입니다. 의뢰인에게 돌려주면 보상을 받을 것입니다.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bad_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>과학자들이 사람들을 정신파 에미션으로부터 보호하기 위해 만든 프로토타입입니다. 교정이 필요합니다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bad_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>교정되지 않은 정신파 보호 헬멧</text>
	</string>

	<string id="good_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>과학자들이 사람들을 정신파 에미션으로부터 보호하기 위해 만든 프로토타입입니다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>정신파 보호 헬멧</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cit_doctors_key_short_desc">
		<text>프리피야트에 있는 비밀 은닉처를 여는 닥터의 열쇠입니다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_name">
		<text>닥터의 열쇠</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_desc">
		<text>측면에 "호텔 폴리샤 - 26호실" 이라고 쓰여 있는 열쇠입니다.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_name">
		<text>스트렐록의 원고</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_desc">
		<text>가죽 표지로 된 낡은 원고입니다. 스트렐록이 직접 썼습니다.\n제목만 보고 판단했을 때는, 존의 비밀들 중 일부가 설명되어 있는 듯합니다.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cit_doctors_pda_name">
		<text>닥터의 쪽지</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_pda_desc">
		<text>"그저 늙은이가 생각하는 음모론을 적어두었을 뿐이라네.".\n\n아그로포롬 시설이 2006년의 그 사건이 일어나기 전에 한 비공식 연구소의 위장 기관으로 쓰여졌다는 소문이 있다네. 그 연구소에서는 다수의 매우 의심스러운 실험이 진행되었다고 하네. 상인들이 이런 연구시설에 대한 많은 정보를 파헤쳐 왔지. 내가 전에 바텐더를 만났을 때, 그가 말하길 듀티 정찰대를 X-18이라고 불리는, 검은 계곡 속의 지하실 안으로 보냈었는데, 그들이 사라졌다고 하더군. 또한 "싸이-브레인"이라고 불리는 메커니즘과 관련된 다른 소문도 있다네. 안타 호수 주변의 모든 곳은 그 쓰레기같은 것의 영향력이 미치고 있다네. 그건 일정 범위 안으로 들어가는 모든 사람들을 좀비로 만들어 버린다고 하더군. 붉은 숲에 있는 레이더 기지 지하에는 X19 연구소라 불리는 다른 기계장치도 있다네, 그리고 그곳이 바로 브레인 스코처일 가능성이 가장 높은 곳이지. 브레인 스코처의 존재 자체가 북쪽으로 가는 길을 고의적으로 막고 있다는 것을 암시하는 증거가 있긴 하지만, 아무도 그게 정확히 어떤 것인지 알지는 못한다네. 바텐더는 브레인 스코처를 인간이 만들었고, 그곳의 메커니즘은 언제나 전력으로 가동되는 것은 아니라고 생각하더군. 그는 브레인 스코처가 잠시 열을 식히는 동안에는 동력이 낮아질 때가 있을 거라고 생각한다네. 이제 존에 있는 모든 지하 연구소를 찾아가 그것들이 숨기고 있는 비밀이 무엇인지 밝혀내야만 하네. 안타깝게도, 난 그런 일을 하기엔 너무 늙었다네. 스트렐록이 아직 여기에 있었으면 좋았으련만, 제기랄, 이미 몇 년 전에 사라져 버렸다더군.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_decoder_desc">
		<text>강력한 전자식 문따개입니다. 이상한 이야기지만, 이 물건은 모든 문을 따기 위해 만들어진 도구는 아닌 것으로 보입니다. 오히려, 이 물건은 특수한 전자적 자물쇠만 열도록 설계된 것으로 보이며 그 밖의 다른 것들을 해제하는 데 쓰이지는 못합니다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_name">
		<text>해독기</text>
	</string>

	<string id="pri_decoder_docs_conclusion_txt">
		<text>문서에는 팽과 스트렐록이 어떻게 숨겨진 실험실에 침투했으며 거기서 어떤 일들을 했는지에 대한 짧은 보고서가 실려있습니다. 또한 체르노빌 원자력 발전소 안과 주변에 있는 거대한 모노리스 세력에 대해서도 언급되어 있습니다. 발전소를 덮은 콘크리트 석관 아래에 대해서도 더욱 자세히 설명되어 있으며, 또한 그곳이 모노리스의 작전 본부같은 무언가를 숨기려는 의도도 존재할 것이라는 가설을 제시했습니다. 그 뒤에는 그들이 발전소 아래쪽으로부터 더 북쪽으로 간 지점에 있는 숨겨진 연구소를 찾아냈다는 사실이 언급되어 있지만, 문서가 쓰여질 당시에는 출입에 필요한 해독기가 없었기 때문에 들어갈 수 없었다고 적혀있습니다.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_quest_case_02_desc">
		<text>군용 문서 및 아그로프롬 근처에서 수행된 조사들의 보고서들이 들어있는 방화처리된 서류가방입니다. 보고서에는 시설로부터 기계장치들과 장비들이 어떻게 사라졌으며, 그 장비들이 어디에 있는지에 대한 조사 결과가 어떻게 조작되었는지에 대한 자세한 정보들이 서술되어 있습니다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_quest_case_02_name">
		<text>군용 문서들</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x18_name">
		<text>생물학 연구 보고서</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x18_desc">
		<text>이 보고서에는 X-18 연구소에서 보내진 생물학적 표본 연구의 세부적인 정보들이 쓰여 있습니다. 표본들은 다양한 강도의 정보적인 필드 효과에 노출되었습니다. 보고서에는 에미션에 노출되었을 때 생명체가 어떻게 변이되는지를 상세하게 설명되어 있습니다.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x16_desc">
		<text>보고서에는 생체 연구 과정에서의 부차적인 발견들 중 하나가 언급되었는데, 특히 생명체가 유도된 정신파 에미션을 만들어낼 수 있다는 발견에 대해 서술되었습니다. 생체적인 필드 방출기, 특히 거대한 두뇌 같은 것들이 X16 연구소에서 진행되는 연구의 일부분으로서 배양되었습니다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x16_name">
		<text>정신파 연구 서류</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x10_desc">
		<text>The documents describe the technical characteristics of an antenna and how they deviate from their planned designs. There is a note on the reverse side which indicates that these documents were prepared in lab X19.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x10_name">
		<text>Rainbow emitter documents</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x8_desc">
		<text>The document refers to the transfer of the research team and all materials to another laboratory far in the north, which will be used to research matters relating to the influence of the noosphere. To enter the lab, use the date of the accident as the code (ddmmyyyy).\n \nThe research team comprised: N.A. Lebedev, E.F. Kalancha and V.I. Suslov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x8_name">
		<text>Order of Transfer</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_jup_ug_desc">
		<text>The notebook contains a detailed description of an experiment assessing a psi-field's effect on an object in another hemisphere. A group of scientists in the Caribbean received the signal, but it was distorted. The signal was altered in a strange way, as though corrected by someone. A possible explanation is that the noosphere theory is correct and the changes were made by the noosphere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_jup_ug_name">
		<text>Experiment notebook</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_mon_con_name">
		<text>Prototype weapon report</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_mon_con_name_desc">
		<text>Documents which describe the operating mechanism and main technical characteristics of a more advanced electromagnetic device.\nThere is a note inside the documents which reads: 'Documents must be returned to X8, the central laboratory. I will be busy, so deliver them yourself. — N. Lebedev'</text>
	</string>

	<string id="quest_package_name">
		<text>Package</text>
	</string>
	<string id="quest_package_desc">
		<text>The content of this package is unknown.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] personal belongings\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_jup_b32_scanner_device_name">
		<text>Anomalous Activity Scanner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b32_scanner_device_desc">
		<text>This case combines an artefact detector, a battery and a powerful transmitter. The device will scan anomalies to determine the number and type of artefacts that appear. All of this information will be automatically relayed to the scientists' bunker.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	

	<!-- MLR -->
	<string id="mlr_strelok_item_01">
		<text>Worn notebook</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mlr_strelok_item_01_desc">
		<text>A notebook, likely owned by Strelok himself. It describes in detail how to get into an underground complex called X-18.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="blackbox_mlr">
		<text>Flight recorder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="blackbox_mlr_descr">
		<text>A flight data recorder, or a "black box". Flight recorders are used to record the status of internal systems and crew conversations, and can provide vital information in the event of an accident. In the Zone, stalker and military personnel alike are interested in these devices.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="item_pda_map_mlr_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_pda_map_mlr_descr">
		<text>A PDA containing possible information on routes between different areas.</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<!-- DRX -->
	<string id="drx_x8_documents_name">
		<text>Antennas installation documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x8_documents_desc">
		<text>The document refers to what seems to be a massive radar installation. Most likely Brain Scorcher structure and operating system.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_x16_documents_name">
		<text>Biological research</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x16_documents_desc">
		<text>A set of old papers that refer to experiments done on rats and other animals.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_x18_documents_name">
		<text>Experiment report: B0-D4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x18_documents_desc">
		<text>Old documents that refer to an experiment related to psy-waves resonance and emitting.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_x19_documents_name">
		<text>Communication log / 21.03.2006</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x19_documents_desc">
		<text>A printed transcription of the radio transmission between scientist groups from the institute.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_agr_u_documents_name">
		<text>Agroprom institute documentation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_agr_u_documents_desc">
		<text>A bunch of notes, pictures and a single marked map regarding Agroprom. Probably written by Strelok himself while being around.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_jup_u_documents_name">
		<text>Transportation records</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_jup_u_documents_desc">
		<text>These documents refer to old records of transporting mechanical equipment and tools to the factory in Jupiter. It also includes geometric schemes for the tunnels toward the eastern side.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="lx8_history_documents_name">
		<text>Experimentation (11.04.2005)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_documents_desc">
		<text>This log documents the results of an experiment happened long years ago regarding new types of psy-emitters.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_2_documents_name">
		<text>Experimentation (24.09.2005)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_2_documents_desc">
		<text>This log documents the results of an experiment happened long years ago regarding psy-waves applications.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_3_documents_name">
		<text>Experimentation (02.05.2006)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_3_documents_desc">
		<text>This log documents the results of a biological experiment.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
