<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<!--===========================================================
<
< TEXT  STRINGS FOR TASKS ON YANTAR MAP
<	CoC 1.4.08 - DoctorX Questlines 1.6
<
<	Modified by: DoctorX
<	Last revised: October 07, 2016
<
<===========================================================-->

<string_table>


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- STORYLINE TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist) Default Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_default_task_name">
		<text>다음 임무를 받기.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_default_task_text">
		<text>당신의 다음 임무를 받아라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_default_task_about">
		<text>뭐? 아, 그래, 스토커, 자네가 내 동료중 한명을 도와주었음 하네. 그럼 어서! 그자에게 가게나!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_default_task_finish">
		<text>행운을 비네 스토커.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist) Research Documents Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_name">
		<text>사하로프 의 연구 문서</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_text">
		<text>사하로프 란 교수의 연구 논문이 돌연변이 공격으로 인해 그의 연구원 동료들이 도망치다가 떨어트렸다. 문서를 확보하고 사하로브 에게 돌려줘라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_about">
		<text>자네가 와서 기쁘네. 내 연구원 중 한명이 현장에서 막 돌아왔는데, 그가 거기서 돌연변이 의 공격을 받을때 그 공책을 놓쳐버렸다네. 그는 거기에 돌아가길 두려워 하고 있고. 난 그 연구 자료가 필요하네 스토커. 내게 다시 가져와주게, 그럼 자네에게 들어간 수고를 내 기꺼이 보상해주겠네.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_finish">
		<text>고맙네 스토커! 여기, 자네의 몫 받아가게.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist) Abnormal Measurement Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_name">
		<text>비정상적 반응 측정</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_text_0">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 당신에게 비정상적인 이상현상 측정을 도와주는것을 물었다. 그전에 당신이 잃어버린 $item_1 를 되찾아라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_text_1">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 당신에게 비정상적인 이상현상 측정을 도와주는것을 물었다.\n표시된 지역으로 이동해라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_text_2">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 당신에게 비정상적인 이상현상 측정을 도와주는것을 물었다.\n측정하기 위해 $item_1 을 사용하라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_text_3">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 당신에게 비정상적인 이상현상 측정을 도와주는것을 물었다.\n $item_1 의 기록 결과와 함께 그에게 복귀하라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_about">
		<text>아! 자네가 올줄 알았네. 우리의 스캐너가 특정한 이상현상에서 흥미로운 판독값을 보여줘서 말일세. 그곳에 가서 좀더 자세히 조사할 경험있는 스토커가 내게 필요하네. 젊은이, 자네에게 딱맞는 장치가 내게 있네. 행운을 빌지.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_finish">
		<text>좋았어! 고맙네 스토커, 이제야 내 연구를 시작할수 있겠어! 정말 잘했네.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist) Search Lab X-18 (Dark Valley) Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_3_name">
		<text>X-18 연구소 조사</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_3_text">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 검은계곡 의 X-18 연구소 에 있는 연구 문서를 필요로 한다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_3_about">
		<text>자네에게 중요한 일이 있네. X-18 연구소에서 중요한 연구가 실시되었다만, 우리가 분석할려고 접근할수가 없네. 우릴 위해 자네가 그걸 찾아올수 있겠나? 가능한다면 내가 보상을 후하게 주겠네.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_3_finish">
		<text>훌륭해! 고맙네 스토커!</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist) Plant Anomaly Scanner (Red Forest) Storyline Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_name">
		<text>심비온트 이상현상 근처에 스캐너 설치</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 붉은숲 의 심비온트 이상현상 근처에다 이상현상 스캐너를 설치하길 원한다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text0">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 붉은숲 의 심비온트 이상현상 근처에다 이상현상 스캐너를 설치하길 원한다.\n먼저 이상현상 스캐너를 얻어라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text1_0">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 붉은숲 의 심비온트 이상현상 근처에다 이상현상 스캐너를 설치하길 원한다.\n이상현상 지역으로 스캐너를 가져가라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text1_1">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 붉은숲 의 심비온트 이상현상 근처에다 이상현상 스캐너를 설치하길 원한다.\n이상현상 지역으로 스캐너를 가져가라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text2">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 붉은숲 의 심비온트 이상현상 근처에다 이상현상 스캐너를 설치하길 원한다.\n스캐너를 설치하라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_text3">
		<text>사하로프 교수가 붉은숲 의 심비온트 이상현상 근처에다 이상현상 스캐너를 설치하길 원한다.\n성과 를 보고하라.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_about">
		<text>훌륭해! 이 새로운 스캐너를 한번 보게나. 우린 이 장치를 이용해 과학적 탐험을 위한 이상현상 활동을 조사할걸세. 그중 존에서 가장 흥미로운 이상현상들이 바로 붉은 숲 깊은 곳에서 발견된 심비온트 이상현상 이지. 우린 이 스캐너를 그 이상현상 근처에 설치하길 원하네. 그럼 그 활동으로 부터 우리가 연구하는데 도움을 줄수있겠지.
		\n그 장소는 위험하지만, 바라건대 자네같이 걸맞은 스토커에겐 큰 문제가 아니겠지. 부디 날 위해 그걸 설치해주게, 그럼 자네에게 들어간 수고를 내 기꺼이 보상해주겠네.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_finish">
		<text>고맙네! 이제 우리가 그 현상을 연구할수 있겠어!</text>

	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- CHANGE FACTIONS TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecologist Trader) Payoff Change Factions Task -->

	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_cf_task_1_name">
		<text>과학 과 절차</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_cf_task_1_text">
		<text>사하로프 가 당신을 공식적인 과학자로 등록시키기 위해 필요한 모든 정부 서류를 제출할 수 있도록 그에게 17,000 루블을 주길 원한다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_cf_task_1_about">
		<text>난 자네가 뛰어난 현장 조수가 될꺼라 생각하네, 하지만 문제는 그 모든 서류를 작업하는데 드는 돈이 저렴하지 않는데다, 어... 동기부여 도 없으면 빨리 되지 않겠지. 자네도 정부쪽 타입이 어떤건지 알잖나.\n \n영구 계약, 라이센스, 신분증 같은것들. 특히 자네의 결과를 생전내로 보고 싶다면, 내게 적어도 17,000 루블 만큼 필요하네. 만약 그만한 돈을 낼 수 있다면, 우린 자네를 기꺼이 받아드리겠네!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_yan_stalker_sakharov_cf_task_1_finish">
		<text>좋아! 훌륭해! 이제 이곳을 자네 집이라 여겨주게, 동료 연구원.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- \\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\ -->


	<!-- /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
	<!--
	<!-- DYNAMIC TASK TEXT  STRINGS
	<!--
	<!--	Modified by DoctorX
	<!--	for DoctorX Questlines 1.6
	<!--	October 07, 2016
	<!--
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Semenov (Ecog Honcho) Research Hunt Task -->

	<string id="yan_ecolog_semenov_task_1_name">
		<text>세메네프 연구 사냥</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_ecolog_semenov_task_1_text">
		<text>세메네프 조수가 해당 주위를 돌아다니면서 신선한 돌연변이 조직 견본을 얻거나 그의 스캐닝 장비로 사체를 분석할수 있도록 당신에게 호위를 요청하였다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_ecolog_semenov_task_1_about">
		<text>내가 조직 견본을 얻고 읽을수 있도록 몇마리 돌연변이들 좀 처리해줄 생각이 있나? 한... 서로 다른 다섯 마리 정도 말일세. 내 목숨을 자네 손에 맡길테니, 자네는 나에게 안전을 보장해주게. 그러면 내가 자네의 수고를 보상하겠네.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_ecolog_semenov_task_1_finish">
		<text>도와줘서 고맙네 친구. 내게 필요한 모든 조직을 얻었으니, 자네의 몫은 여기있네. 언제 한번 날보러 오게나.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Sakharov (Ecog Trader) -->
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_name">
		<text>얀타 벙커를 위해 %s 을(를) 구하라</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_text">
		<text>사하로브 교수의 최근 실험에 필요한 %s 의 신선한 조직 견본이 필요하다. 내가 찾을수 있는 한 그에게 전달해야한다.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_about">
		<text>경험있는 스토커나 돌연변이 사냥꾼 이 내게 필요하네. 그게 자네인가?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>난 %s 의 조직 견본 으로부터 신선한 세포를 채집해야 하네. 그럴려면, 자네가, 어... 그 견본을 구해서, 내 벙커에 가져다 주게. 나도 동물학자들 이걸 원치 않는건 알지만, 여기가 동물원이 아니라는 점 은 인정해야하네. 어쨋든, 자네가 그 필요한 샘플을 가지자 마자 나에게 돌아오게. 그것이 야생 돌연변이의 생물학에 대한 귀중한 통찰력을 제공할수도 있네!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>고맙네, 친구. 이게 내 연구에 큰 도움이 될 것이네.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Collect New Artefact Task -->
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_name">
		<text>Anomalous Research</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_text">
		<text>Professor Sakharov has asked me to find a %s artefact to help fund his research.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_about">
		<text>Would you like to assist me with some research? I will pay you for your efforts.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>Our research team is near the brink of another significant discovery, but desperately needs more materials to maintain our funding and continue experimentation! Please, locate and deliver us one %s artefact. We'll need to take samples from it if we hope to continue our investigations and provide raw material for our suppliers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>On behalf of the scientific community, I thank you. Here is your reward, as promised.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Classified Information Task -->
	<string id="classified_information_task_name">
		<text>Classified Information</text>
	</string>
	<string id="classified_information_task_text">
		<text>The professor has asked me to obtain some sensitive research documents for him.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="classified_information_task_about">
		<text>Unknown brigands have accosted one of our research teams. Fortunately, part of the expedition came back alive and well. Unfortunately, they had to leave somewhat sensitive research behind during their escape.\n \nFor the sake of scientific progress, as well as the future wellbeing of my colleagues, I do not wish this data to remain lost - or worse, find their way into the hands of whatever mysterious group attacked my researchers. Please, go to the cache at these coordinates: if you hurry, the documents I wish to recover should still be there.  For your discretion, as well as the delivery of these documents to my office here, I offer a reasonable payment. As a further token of my gratitude, you may also help yourself to whatever supplies my team may have left behind in that cache. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="classified_information_task_finish">
		<text>Thank you, dear stalker. Or should I say colleague? Research can now continue smoothly - hopefully without any additional hiccups coming around the corner. </text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- yan_stalker_sakharov -->
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_psi_helmet_upgrade_name">
		<text>Collect the Psy-Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_psi_helmet_upgrade_text">
		<text>Professor Sakharov has agreed to fully calibrate your psy-protection helmet. He has asked you to return to pick it up after about two days.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="brain_machine_deactivate_name">
		<text>Disable the Miracle Machine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="brain_machine_deactivate_text">
		<text>The Miracle Machine may cause issues for the scientists at Yantar if left unchecked for too long. Professor Sakharov would surely appreciate its deactivation.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- -->
	<!-- Peregrine (Military Mechanic) Find Level 1 Toolkit Task -->

	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_1_name">
		<text>Find %s for Peregrine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_1_text">
		<text>%s are required by Peregrine to install basic equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_1_about">
		<text>Oh, sure. HQ notified us of tools arriving at our bunker via the Cordon, but the package never made it. And where did this delivery end up? Only the Zone knows. However, the situation hasn't changed, and we still need more tools. HQ is real obstinate about organising more for us right now, so I'll tell you what. If you manage to find some tools out in the wild - even some basic ones - I'll personally pay you to bring them back here. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_1_fetch_about">
		<text>Brilliant. Just focus on bringing back a set of basic tools for now - more advanced stuff is useless without them. Good hunting out there, stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_1_fetch_finish">
		<text>Alright, let's take a look. Yeah, these'll do. Now maybe I can do something other than maintenance. Here's your bounty. Thanks for your help.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_2_name">
		<text>Find %s for Peregrine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_2_text">
		<text>%s are required by Peregrine to install advanced equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_2_about">
		<text>Well, you're certainly more enterprising than my usual suppliers, so tell you what - get me a more advanced set of tools. Do this, and there'll be money in your pocket. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_2_fetch_about">
		<text>Fantastic. I'm sure Sakharov will appreciate this too.  I'm sure that, once you bring me these tools, my technical work will be helping him fund his bunker before you can blink.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_2_fetch_finish">
		<text>Great! Come back any time if you need me to take a look at your gear. I'll be able to do some half-decent modifications now, thanks to you.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_3_name">
		<text>Find %s for Peregrine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_3_text">
		<text>%s are required by Peregrine to install expert equipment upgrades, I should bring them back to him if I find any.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_3_about">
		<text>I'm not sure if he's told you, but Sakharov is quite pleased that you're helping me out like this. He wanted me to tell you he's set aside a healthy sum of roubles for the stalker who can bring me a set of expert tools. It should let us get the most out of the scientific gear we keep here - particularly our hazmat suits and exoskeletons. So, are you willing to go toolkit hunting for me one last time? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_3_fetch_about">
		<text>I'm honestly grateful for this. When you get back with the tools, I'll also show you a trick or two on how to do proper field maintenance - unless another technician has taught you already, of course. It'll be my way of saying thanks. Good luck out there. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mechanic_army_yan_mlr_task_3_fetch_finish">
		<text>Hm. Pity you don't work in the Supply Corps. Maybe now I can finally get that damn receiver fixed. As for you, you've earned my gratitude. On behalf of this bunker, here is your payment. </text>
	</string>
	
	
	
 	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_name">
		<text>Recover the Tracking Device</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_about">
		<text>We have implanted several devices on mutants to measure various data - heart rate, feeding habits, sleep cycles, travel times and the like. However, since the last blowout, one of the devices has started malfunctioning - it still tracks movement but has otherwise ceased to transmit any other useful data. As these trackers are of an especially advanced design, we must retrieve the faulty one for inspection and possible repairs.  Obtain the device from the mutant by any means available to you, then bring it back to us. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_stage_0">
		<text>Stop the mutant with the tracking device</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_stage_1">
		<text>Recover the tracking device</text>
	</string>
	<string id="yan_stalker_sakharov_task_4_stage_2">
		<text>Return the device</text>
	</string>
	<string id="recover_mutant_data_device_desc">
		<text>A sturdy device that was planted on a mutant to monitor its movements, habits and vital signs. Shows signs of corrosion, and is covered in numerous bite and scratch marks.  </text>
	</string>
	<string id="recover_mutant_data_device_name">
		<text>Tracking device</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
